Can you speak to the benefits of
optimizing omega-3 intake and what kind
of dose you're taking at the moment?
Because I think you even take a higher
dose than me.
>> Four grams DHA, two grams EPA.
So that's four giant triple strength in
the morning, four giant triple strength
at bedtime.
I take and it's it's so useful for a lot
of things. brain health, heart health,
androgen receptor density, almost every
system in your body. It's one of those
things where you [__] have to take
it. Like, it's the most critical
important over-the-counter supplement
you could take for your health. Like,
step one. Like, you know, when you go to
countries where they don't have shoes,
that's how I look at people who don't
take fish oil. Like, wow. Look at that
[__] savage.
>> Yep.
>> Only, you know, the thing is people who
don't have shoes, they develop calluses
on the soles of their feet. They don't
need shoes. But you watching this,
you need the omega-3s. I remember once I
was talking to an exceptionally stupid
woman and it happens a lot actually, but
I remember this time in particular and
she was telling me how she
insists on breastfeeding because it has
omega-3s. I'm like, "Bitch, you eat
Froot Loops for three meals a day. You
don't have any omega-3s to give." She's
like, "What?" I was like, "What do you
think? You're just your titties just
generate omega-3s out of the atmosphere?
You have to eat the omega-3s and then
your breast pump what you eat into your
baby. If you eat like [__] your baby's
going to become out as dumb as you. And
then, you know, she never talked to me
again after that. But I think she did
start taking omega-3s. At least she
still eats Froot Loops.
It's it's it's one of the I I one of my
first jobs out of university was to do a
marketing uh catalog for a big
supplement retailer in Australia. And
you know, I was working at a gym. I had
a degree in marketing. It was very
interesting. And one of the things you
learn is that almost all supplements are
[__] Uh there's a few that are
good. Your your intra workout product is
fantastic. By the way, um
it was when I saw that you had some
products, I was like, "Okay, they've got
some cool labels on them. They've got
some cool names. I hope they're not full
bullshit." And then I was looking at the
ingredient panel. I was like, "Oh, no.
This is this is actually what people
need for an intro." So the the thing
with the omega-3 is I mean I've tried
every supplement that's actually healthy
and the thing that is the most
profoundly impactful that I actually
feel if I take it consistently over time
is the high dose omega-3. It is and it's
something that I recommend for all my
clients sometimes yeah you know it it
adds up a little bit in price but it is
absolutely worthwhile because it's the
most evidence-based supplement. And when
you actually run people's omega-3 index
when they're not taking any, unless they
absolutely love eating salmon and
mackerel, which most people don't, their
omega-3 index is in the absolute [__]
j.
>> I've never I've been too scared to look.
Like I like it's like, you know, I'm not
going to take a pulse on a headless
body. So, like I don't see why I would
run an omega-3 index in somebody with a
high school education who tells me that
they take two cc's of test every other
week. I'm like, yeah, there's no way
that this [__] is doing anything
right. I'm not even going to bother.
It's like, first, before you even get
blood work on him, let me fix everything
I can in his life and let him do
something right for four weeks. Because
if I do blood work on him now, I'm gonna
have to tell him he's dying and he's
going to be too scared to function and
he's just going to say [__] it and start
banging hookers and starting coke off
their ass and blow his kids college
funds. So, I got to at least give him
some hope for survival and fix
everything for a month and then we'll
check his blood work and see what he's
like. And then they're like, I want to
use Master. I want to do this. I want to
do that. It's like, okay, [__] First do
HRT and eat healthy and train for a
month and then I promise I promise if
you're healthy enough I will give you
permission to use something more extreme
like master and it's like a it's not a
placebo dose but it's like if I have to
negotiate with somebody and be like all
right I'll give you the thumbs up on the
mastron if I can see your apo under 90.
It doesn't do anything test doesn't do.
You haven't even figured out how much
test you're supposed to be using yet,
but you misunderstood my videos and you
are obsessed with this drug because you
don't understand what it is. And you
don't get that it's basically test
little brother, but it's test little
brother without a prison record and
without a warrant out for its arrest.
It's still test little brother. It's
just test little brother without the
baggage. So, but you're not even healthy
enough to do this. So, it's like until
you could get that APOB under 90, you're
not using any mastron. You're not using
any anavar. Till you can get that GGT
under 30, you're not touching DHB.
And then, and there's no reason to even
[__] with the other drugs because those
are the three cleanest drugs you can
use.
I often I often use the analogy for
people who are who are starting TRT who
don't have their [__] together is that
they're basically taking a Ferrari
engine and putting it in the sweet swift
and then when the car crashes and it
blows up when it comes out of parking
lot then they're blaming the car and
it's like the issue is you didn't
service the rest of the car one and two
you don't know how to drive and they
they think that if they put the Ferrari
engine it's going to turn the rest of
the car into the Ferrari and then
they're going to turn into a race car
driver and it's like that not only does
that not happen but you're going to
[__] fall apart. And we see it all
the time.
>> I always like I'm like like first we
have to hit the straightaway, then you
can punch the nitrous.
>> But we're on a curve right now. There's
no point in punching the nitrous right
now. You're just going to wreck the car.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And half the time when I see the guys,
they're not even on the road. They're
off in the ditch and the car's on fire.
What I always say to people too is like
it's like you know when you give a
four-year-old the the um let the foury
old sit in the driver's seat and they're
turning the wheel and they're saying
vroom vroom and hitting the horn and
their feet don't touch the pedals and
they don't even know about keys so
there's no key in the ignition. That's
you
like first let me let let's first let's
have your feet touch the pedals and
stick the key in the ignition. Let's
master that. Once we get the nutrition
and the training right, once we've
turned the key in the ignition, which is
nutrition, and once we've got our feet
on the pedals, which is training, now we
can actually start turning the wheel and
we're driving a car.
And and and also, it's like, let's let's
have you be the guy who's been doing
that for a while because people go, "Oh,
I fixed my diet and I started training
eight weeks ago." I'm like, "Okay, cool.
But all your cells and everything in
your body has been built on garbage thus
far. So let's give it some more time to
take some effect and then let's look at
having some expectations about results.
>> Yeah, I send a lot of people over to
Todd's content to learn about stuff that
is outside of my scope. Todd does
consults as well. So can you let people
know how they can find you and how they
can work with you if that's
>> If you go with the YouTube channel,
please watch the most important [__]
playlist. I called it most important
[__] for a reason because it's the most
important [__] The reason why I use
that language is because my signature
that every video starts with me saying
you're watching Dr. Todd Lee TV where
theoretically you could learn a bunch of
cool [__] So then the name of the
playlist is the most important [__] So
that is the [__] you should watch first.
Like it I wish there was a way to force
it so that no one could watch anything
but that playlist first then
watch whatever the [__] you want. Most
people watch T-ball and trend and they
skip hydration and then they're just
going to end up with a [__] up organ
systems because they got their
priorities all [__] up. Now if you
want my help on my Instagram there's a
link to get a consult or you could just
go toddled.com.
That's my name. put a.com after it.
You're there and I will do a consult
with you. I mean, a lot of people are
smart and they're busy and they don't
have time to watch my [__] They're just
like, I'm sold. This is the guy. I don't
have time to watch his [__] I just want
to talk to that doesn't make you have a
low IQ. I was [__] with you. So, just
get the consult and then I can I have
programs whether it's coaching or
concierge wellness. I'll find the right
program for you with the consult. If you
want blood work read and analyzed, that
is not a consult. That is a blood work
analysis. That's a different option on
the website. That's pretty much it.
That's that's the long and the short of
it.